<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
      xmlns:thr="http://purl.org/syndication/thread/1.0"
      xml:lang="en-us">
  <link rel="self" href="http://yqrashawn.com/feeds/lazyblorg-all.atom_1.0.links-and-teaser.xml" />
  <title type="text">infin</title>
  <id>http://yqrashawn.com/</id>
  <link href="http://yqrashawn.com" />
  <icon>/favicon.ico</icon>
  <updated>2017-10-29T20:51:07+08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>yqrashawn</name>
  </author>
  <subtitle type="text">infin</subtitle>
  <rights>All content written by yqrashawn</rights>
  <generator uri='https://github.com/novoid/lazyblorg'>Generated from Org-mode source code using lazyblorg which is written in Python. Industrial-strength technology, baby.</generator>
<!-- ############################################################################################# -->
<entry>
    <title type="text">My Karabiner Elements configuration</title>
    <link href='http://yqrashawn.com/2017/10/29/my-karabiner-configuration' />
    <published>2017-10-29T20:45:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-29T20:45:00+08:00</updated>
    <category scheme='http://yqrashawn.com/tags/coding' term='coding' />
    <category scheme='http://yqrashawn.com/tags/tool' term='tool' />
    <category scheme='http://yqrashawn.com/tags/efficient' term='efficient' />
    <category scheme='http://yqrashawn.com/tags/karabiner' term='karabiner' />
    <summary type='xhtml'>
<div xmlns='http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml'>
<p>

This post are descriptions and tutorial of my <a href="https://github.com/yqrashawn/yqdotfiles/blob/master/.config/karabiner/karabiner.json">personal KE complex modification</a>.

</p>


<p>

I <a href="https://github.com/pqrs-org/KE-complex_modifications/pull/162">merged</a> my personal <a href="https://github.com/tekezo/Karabiner-Elements">Karabiner Elements</a> configuration into the <a href="https://github.com/pqrs-org/KE-complex_modifications">official repo</a> several days ago. You can import my personal rules <a href="https://pqrs-org.github.io/KE-complex_modifications/">here</a>. To achieve efficiency, I use karabiner with <a href="https://www.alfredapp.com/">Alfred</a> mainly through <a href="https://www.alfredapp.com/help/workflows/triggers/external/">alfred workflow external trigger</a> and <a href="https://developer.apple.com/legacy/library/documentation/Darwin/Reference/ManPages/man1/osascript.1.html">osascript</a> (command line tool for calling AppleScript code).

</p>


<p>

Here is these configurations. Please note that I update my configurations everyday. So I  can't keep this post up to date. The key here is to introduce a system for launching apps, invoking scripts and all stuffs that can be done with shell (everything). When you can get anything you want with few key strokes, <b>it feels great</b>.

</p>


<p>

<a href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/qepdfdu0djyed7v/workflows.zip?dl=0">Download all my workflow from dropbox</a>, please contact <a href="https://github.com/yqrashawn">me</a> when this link broken. I may update this post for each specific config if I have time in the future (may not happen). If you have any problems or ideas, please <a href="https://github.com/yqrashawn/yqdotfiles/issues/new">open an issue</a> in my dotfile repo. And you can also check <a href="https://github.com/pqrs-org/KE-complex_modifications">Ke-complex_modifications</a> official repo for more rules and discussion.

</p>

<ul>
<li>Alfred Mode (z)
<ul>
<li>Press z down then click other keys to trigger Alfred workflow</li>
<li>This mode severely relays on Alfred Workflow, links of workflow will update later.
<ul>
<li>y: Hyper + = trigger youdao workflow</li>
<li>j: Search github</li>
<li>tab: Switch to chosen iTerm session</li>
<li>x: Kill process</li>
<li>t: Launch Tower.app with chosen repo</li>
<li>b: Switch chosen to browser tab</li>
<li>r: Open recent download file</li>
<li>l: Trigger Alfred File Action in Finder.app</li>
<li>l: Trigger devtool in browsers</li>
<li>o: Copy selection into emacs for temp edit</li>
<li>p: Paste the saved temp buffer back</li>
<li>;: Open localhost with entered port number</li>
<li>q: Use Keyboard Maestro record macro</li>
<li>]: Play last macro once</li>
</ul></li>
</ul></li>
<li>yq Launch Mode (w)
<ul>
<li>Press w down then click other keys to bring application to front.</li>
<li>Press w down then press [ down to enter second level of this mode.</li>
<li>This mode severely relays on Alfred Workflow, links of workflow will update later.
<ul>
<li>j: iTerm</li>
<li>k: Emacs</li>
<li>l: Google Chrome</li>
<li>c: Safari</li>
<li>m: Mail</li>
<li>t: Tower</li>
<li>b: BearyChat</li>
<li>v: WeChat</li>
<li>[r: Reeder</li>
</ul></li>
</ul></li>
<li>Quick Insert Mode (period)
<ul>
<li>Press period down then click other keys to insert or trigger workflow.</li>
<li>Press period down then press comma down to enter second level of this mode.</li>
<li>Some rules in this mode need to use with some specific emacs key-bindings.
<ul>
<li>tab: control+tab emacs:(switch-to-second-most-recent-buffer)</li>
<li>comma+tab: control+tab emacs:(switch-to-third-most-recent-buffer)</li>
<li>a: insert ~/</li>
<li>s: insert .*</li>
<li>slash: insert ./</li>
<li>q: insert {</li>
<li>comma+q: insert }</li>
<li>e: insert (</li>
<li>r: insert )</li>
<li>g: command+control+k alfred clipboard</li>
<li>d: command+control+d Mac OS define</li>
</ul></li>
</ul></li>
<li>Slash Mode (period)
<ul>
<li>Press period down then click other keys to insert or trigger workflow.
<ul>
<li>tab: command+tab switch to previous application</li>
</ul></li>
</ul></li>
<li>Other modifications
<ul>
<li>Mainly bind option and command keys to function keys, and then use with other applications.</li>
<li>MINILA modification aiming to make it more like HHKB.</li>
<li>Modifications with keyboard name in their descriptions can't work on other keyboard.</li>
<li>Caps Lock to escape when pressed alone and to control as modifier key</li>
<li>Control to escape when pressed alone on HHKB and MINILA</li>
<li>Left command to f19 when pressed alone, trigger alfred</li>
<li>Left option to f18 when pressed alone, trigger context</li>
<li>Right option to f17 when pressed alone</li>
<li>Right command to f16 when pressed alone</li>
<li>Right command to command+tab when pressed alone</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>
</div>
    </summary>
    <id>http://yqrashawn.com/2017/10/29/my-karabiner-configuration-from-feed-with-teaser</id>
</entry>
<!-- ############################################################################################# -->
<entry>
    <title type="text">Thought about company knowledge database</title>
    <link href='http://yqrashawn.com/2017/10/28/company-knowledge-database' />
    <published>2017-10-28T23:55:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-28T23:56:00+08:00</updated>
    <category scheme='http://yqrashawn.com/tags/thoughts' term='thoughts' />
    <summary type='xhtml'>
<div xmlns='http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml'>
<p>

Discussed a lot with my colleague today, mainly about problems we are facing and problems our company are facing. There one specific problem caused the majority of other problems. That's why our friends don't have time to learn new things, or why they won't spend time on improving their skill and knowledge while they do feel they need to.

</p>


<p>

In a word, they lack something to invoke their interests for the entry of the adventure to more unknown.

</p>


<p>

For me, I subscribe blogs using RSS. Those blogs are found through my daily question solving or discussing with other developers in open source communities. So I'm totally into these articles and they bring me new things every week, new things that I don't know that don't know. That's the most important thing that one needs when is buried in daily routine.

</p>


<p>

So maybe a company knowledge database can solve this problem. A database that everyone can contribute to and everyone can vote for his/her favorites. Thus, I write this down so that I may build one for my company.

</p>
</div>
    </summary>
    <id>http://yqrashawn.com/2017/10/28/company-knowledge-database-from-feed-with-teaser</id>
</entry>
<!-- ############################################################################################# -->
<entry>
    <title type="text">Halt and Catch Fire</title>
    <link href='http://yqrashawn.com/2017/10/22/after-watching-halt-and-catch-fire' />
    <published>2017-10-22T08:51:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-28T23:38:00+08:00</updated>
    <category scheme='http://yqrashawn.com/tags/watching' term='watching' />
    <summary type='xhtml'>
<div xmlns='http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml'>
<p>

Just finish the Halt and Catch Fire, really great show. It makes me think about that everyone is full of story in their life, amazing to others but definitely not to themselves, like Joe in the series.

</p>


<p>

It's just that I think Joe is "right" in some way. The right is some kind of his every desicion of fresh start, it's so decisive. It makes the character fear nothing. He desires success so much but go through his failer and go for the fresh start so quick. But on the other hand, he is so emotional, about his failer, about Gordon's die.

</p>


<p>

These characters normally can't be on the same person. Maybe that's why it makes me think Joe is "right".

</p>
</div>
    </summary>
    <id>http://yqrashawn.com/2017/10/22/after-watching-halt-and-catch-fire-from-feed-with-teaser</id>
</entry>
<!-- ############################################################################################# -->
<entry>
    <title type="text">About</title>
    <link href='http://yqrashawn.com/about' />
    <published>2017-10-21T10:48:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-21T10:48:00+08:00</updated>
    <summary type='xhtml'>
<div xmlns='http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml'>
<p>

Blog about coding and every other things in daily life.

</p>
</div>
    </summary>
    <id>http://yqrashawn.com/about-from-feed-with-teaser</id>
</entry></feed>